Thomas Imbert

29 Rue de Grenelle **Paris**

+33 646022307

thomas.smart.dev@gmail.com

Summary

I am a front-end developer with 7+ years of experience and a focus on UX. To that end, he has honed his skills in writing succinctly, producing clean and efficient code, and building intuitive products.

I get excited when talking about web apps vs. websites and believe that my value stems from the impact he can have on his client's customers. I have available to work on front-end projects with a focus on UI, JavaScript,

and React.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Web Developer

March 2021-February 2024

- -Rebuilt a major music blog in South Africa, which resulted in a 1500% increase in traffic.
- -Designed and built an events calendar that could be maintained via a Google Docs CSV.
- -Built a recipe database website for a major food brand's product range.
- -Created a showcase and online order system for a wine company.
- -Programmed a tool for users to place orders for prints of their Instagram images.

Firing Squad, Front-end Developer

May 2019- February 2021

- -Built a donation site with rankings where users could nominate people to partake..
- -Created a forum and community engagement website for a major energy drink.
- -Set the internal standard for coding practices and frameworks used by other developers in the company.
- -Managed projects, client expectations, deadlines, and collaboration

SKILLS

Languages

- · HTML
- · CSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- · SCSS/SASS

Librarys

- React
- Angular
- Vue

Tool

- · Git
- · GitHub
- PhotoShop
- · Trello
- NPM
- · YARN

Frameworks

- Bootstrap
- NextIs
- PhotoShop
- · TailWind CSS
- · NextJs
- · TailWind CSS

LANGUAGES

English

with external developers and designers.

-Built a showcase and eCommerce website for a high-performance bicycle company.

Alchemy + Aim, Front-end + Technical Lead

August 2016- April 2019

- -Built and maintained the base framework for all custom projects.
- -Interviewed and assisted new staff during onboarding.
- -Contributed to major business decisions regarding the company's direction.
- -Put together systems to standardize the project workflow among devs.

EDUCATION

Paris Diderot University

Master of Science in Information Technology (MSc(IT)), Computer science

2011 - 2015

PROJECTS

Robustswap

https://robustswap.com/

Apeswap

https://apeswap.finance/

MatrixWorld

https://matrixworld.org/

Cronossteakhouse

https://www.cronossteakhouse.com/